<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Future of Energy]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Future of Energy]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-future-of-energy/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 14:27:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/the-future-of-energy/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICAEW - the future in ten minutes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>ICAEW - the future in ten minutes</h1><p>The UK is a single player on the world stage, and cannot alone impact change with its own actions.  For example, between them as of 2011, the USA, Russia, China, Australia and India hold 72% of the worlds coal reserves, which could last for more than 100 years with current consumption3, and no profit making entity will give up such significant reserves lightly or without serious measures to compensate for the sacrifice.  Other holdings of fossil fuel reserves broadly follow this pattern of a few countries holding a significant proportion of the global reserve. Unfortunately, conscience and science will never prevail in this arena, only money will talk.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0a40cb7969d68108e3996bf5ffbcb7274553cbe8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/146771870</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">96432a7a-5877-4179-b7ae-0fe87a423ee7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 14:27:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Some great minds are thinking about this]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Some great minds are thinking about this</h1><p>Today, we consume a truly vast amount of energy - with demand continuing to skyrocket at an alarming rate. We know that producing this energy has significant environmental impacts and emitting so much carbon dioxide into the atmosphere could cause catastrophic climate change. There is a general consensus among the scientific community that global warming is a real issue and countries are already committed to applying pressure to all consumers to reduce carbon emissions to levels that will allow us to move in to the future with a sustainable strategy.  </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e0ea06b3-9553-4cae-8eb0-bfcb5079f2d0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gz_L6KuqvFI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1bd1df4e-8b70-4a35-994d-f2f3e324082b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 14:19:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The power of a European energy union]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The power of a European energy union</h1><p>By coordinating research and investment, encouraging conservation, and integrating energy markets, an energy union would help fight climate change, provide Europe with a much needed economic stimulus, and protect the continent from supply shocks, such as those caused by the crises in North Africa and Ukraine.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/dca8eda8-8ba4-40b0-8f3d-d9a628af8fa2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://economia.icaew.com/opinion/february-2015/the-power-of-a-european-energy-union</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a21e556d-9f52-47bc-bcf7-55494213658d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 14:19:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nuclear Fusion]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Nuclear Fusion</h1><p>This has the power to undermine the entire debate.  If humanity can establish a stable fusion reaction, we would soon move over to this.  Or create a black hole in the process as always seems to be the case...</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cdcff3f2-442c-4d85-a665-95212e7b4ea8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-future-of-energy/nuclear-fusion/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b13828f7-4801-46b6-8343-4e3f84f77ff7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 13:49:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>